iproacademy.com 2018-12-19

# Privacy Policy - iPro Academy

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of www.iProAcademy.com (the “Site”) owned by iPro Academy, LLC, its subsidiaries, affiliates and partners (“iPro Academy”). iPro Academy values you as our customer and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the type of information we may collect from you or that you may provide to us when you visit the Site, how that information is used and how you can “opt out.” Your use of the Site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this Privacy Policy.

You may contact us via the various methods provided in the contact page.

**Use of Personal Information Collected**  
iPro Academy may collect personally identifiable information from you, meaning information about you that can be used to contact or uniquely identify you (“Personal Information”), only on a voluntary basis. Such Personal Information may include information such as your name, postal address, email address, and telephone number.

We collect Personal Information from you if you request information from us or sign up to join our email lists. Personal Information we collect is internally reviewed and used to improve our Sites, to notify you of updates to our Sites or any products or services we offer, to respond to visitor inquiries, to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights, and to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide your Personal Information to us, such as newsletters. Once your Personal Information is reviewed, it is either discarded or stored on a secure dedicated server hosted by 1Shoppingcart and InboxAir. For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on iPro Academy’s servers. Our payment gateway provider keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

Your Personal Information, including without limitation your email address, will not be sold or provided to third parties except as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will seek to obtain written or active email consent from you if we intend to use information collected from you in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection.

**Other Information Collected Online**  
In some cases, iPro Academy may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable, including through automated means such as cookies. For example, iPro Academy may collect information such as domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address. Cookies enable us to track things in aggregate form such as the total number of visitors to the Site, and the length of the visits to the Site. Such information is stored in iPro Academy’s database. No Personal Information is extracted in this process. The information we collect using automated means is used for internal review to improve the Site, and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

**Information We Share**  
We use third parties to help us provide services to you such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, maintaining our database, administering emails, and administering drawings or contests. Third parties also provide aggregate, comparative information on the performance of our Site to us.

You should be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to enforce or apply our Terms of Use, conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect us, the users of our Site or others.

If we ever merge with, are acquired by or acquire another business entity, some or all of the personal information collected about you may be shared with this entity, as well as retained by us. In the event we transfer any of your information in connection with such a sale, we will post a notice on our website and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser of your information honors your opt-out requests, if any.

Other than as set forth above, we will not share or sell your information to any outside organization without your written or electronically-indicated consent.

**Your Choices**  
If you do not wish for us to use your Personal Information to send you promotions regarding our products or services, you can opt out of such use by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your Personal Information or at any other time by sending an email to support@iPro Academy.com stating your request. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may choose not to receive further promotional emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of such email.

Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our Sites’ features.

How You Can Correct or Remove Information  
If you have submitted Personal Information to us and would like that information deleted from our records or would like to update or correct that information, please click on the “Contact Us” link on our Site and contact us as indicated. iPro Academy will use commercially reasonable efforts to make corrections or remove your Personal Information from our records.

**Non-iPro Academy Sponsors Promotions**  
When a contest/sweepstakes/survey/promotion that is not sponsored by iPro Academy is posted on the Site, you may be asked to supply some personally identifying information such as your name, email address and/or phone number by the third-party company offering the promotion. iPro Academy is not affiliated with such third parties and cannot extend our Privacy Policy to prevent these third parties from using your information in the manner they deem suitable. Please review the terms and conditions of any offers presented before you complete any of the offers.

**Children Under the Age of 13**  
The Site is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information or other information from children under age 13. If you are under 13 years old, do not use or provide any information on or through the Site. If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any Personal Information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact iPro Academy using the contact information provided above.

**Updates and Effective Date**  
iPro Academy reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If there is a material change in our privacy practices, we will indicate on the Site that our privacy practices have changed and provide a link to the new policy. In the event we make a material change to how we use your Personal Information, we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of such new or different use. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of this page. You are responsible for periodically reviewing our Sites and this Privacy Policy to check for any updates or changes.
